Cashfuse Privacy Policy
=======================

TL;DR: For cashfuse.ca visitors, we do not use cookies and we do not collect any personal data. If you decide to create an account, we ask for the bare minimum and only share it with services that are absolutely necessary for the app to function.

At Cashfuse, we are committed to complying with PIPEDA and other privacy regulations on our website and on our web analytics product too. The privacy of your data is a big deal to us.

In this policy, we lay out what data we collect and why, how your data is handled and your rights to your data. We promise we will never distribute or sell your data.

As a visitor to the cashfuse.ca website
---------------------------------------

The privacy of our website visitors is important to us so we do not track any individual people. As a visitor to the cashfuse.ca website:

* No personal information is collected
* No information such as cookies is stored in the browser
* No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties
* No information is shared with advertising companies
* No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends
* No information is monetized

Data collected includes referral sources, top pages, visit duration, information from the devices (device type, operating system, country and browser) used during the visit.

As a customer and subscriber of Cashfuse
----------------------------------------

Our guiding principle is to collect only what we need and that we will solely process this information to provide you with the service you signed up for.

We use a select number of trusted external service providers for certain service offerings. These service providers are carefully selected and meet high data protection, data privacy and security standards.

We only share information with them that is required for the services offered and we contractually bind them to keep any information we share with them as confidential and to process personal data only according to our instructions.

Here’s what that means in practice:

### What we collect and what we use it for

* An email address is required to create an account. You need to provide us with your email address if you want to create a Cashfuse account. That’s just so you can log in and personalize your new account, and we can send you invoices, updates or other essential information.
* Shared Expenses are encrypted on your computer with a private key shared by both you and your contributor. It is impossible for Cashfuse to decrypt this data. To make the sharing possible between you and your contributor, we store your encrypted data on a server. This encrypted data contains: your email and a list of your shared transactions. More specifically: the transaction date, amount and beneficiary.
* All of the data that we collect is kept fully secured, encrypted and hosted on a server in Montréal, Canada. This ensures that all of the site data is being covered by the Canadiens strict laws on data privacy. Your site data never leaves Canada.
* The payment process is handled by a third-party payment provider. If you choose to subscribe to Cashfuse, the billing information and the payment process is handled by Stripe. See the[Stripe Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/en-ca/privacy) for full details.
* When you write to us with a question or to ask for help. We keep that correspondence, which includes the email address, so that we have a history of past correspondences to reference if you reach out in the future. We use this data solely in connection with answering the queries we receive.

### Retention of data

We will retain your information as long as your account is active, as necessary to provide you with the services or as otherwise set forth in this policy.

We will also retain and use this information as necessary for the purposes set out in this policy and to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements and protect Cashfuse’s legal rights.

You can choose todelete your Cashfuse account at any time. To do so, email us delete@cashfuse.ca. All your data will be permanently deleted immediately when you delete your account.

Changes and questions
---------------------

We may update this policy as needed to comply with relevant regulations and reflect any new practices. Whenever we make a significant change to our policies, we will also announce them on our company blog or social media profiles.

[Contact us](mailto:info@cashfuse.ca) if you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this privacy policy, your data, or your rights with respect to your information.

Last updated: September 24th, 2021
